matchbook.com 2015-03-15

# Matchbook.com - Sports Betting Exchange, Lowest Commissions, Best Odds Online

Top

## Introduction

Matchbook is strongly committed to the protection of our clients' “Personal Information” and has designed all services to protect customer privacy and confidentiality.

Personal Information is information you provide to Matchbook and may include your name and address, date of birth and e-mail address. Additional information, such as payment card details, bank account details or online e-wallet account information, may also be provided in the Cashier section.

Throughout the Privacy Policy, references to “Matchbook” will include any or all of its direct and indirect subsidiary undertakings and their related companies or agents as may exist from time to time. References to “we”, “us” or “our” means Matchbook and/or related companies as outlined above.

Matchbook reserves the right to amend the Privacy Policy from time to time. In the event of changes being made the updated Privacy Policy will be posted on site. The continued use of the site by a Member, following any amendments, will constitute acceptance of the new Policy.

Top

## Information collection

We collect two types of information from online activity at Matchbook: general tracking data and user-specific data.

General tracking information is statistical and other analytical information collected on an aggregated basis. It does not identify you as an individual, and is used only to enable us to better understand user requirements.

General tracking data includes information on web traffic, such as a user's browsing activity; IP address; PC operating system; type of browser, and similar details.

User-specific information is particular to each individual user who chooses to provide that information.

User-specific information includes your name and address, date of birth and e-mail address. Additional information, such as payment card details, bank account details or online e-wallet account information, may also be provided in the Cashier section.

Top

## Adwords

This website uses the Google AdWords remarketing service to advertise on third party websites (including Google) to previous visitors to Matchbook.com. This could be in the form of an advertisement on the Google search results page, or a site in the Google Display Network. Third-party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on someone’s past visits to the Matchbook.com website. Of course, any data collected will be used in accordance with our own privacy policy and Google’s privacy policy.

You can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the [Google Ad Preferences page](http://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb/), and if you want to you can opt out of interest-based advertising entirely by [changing your cookie settings](http://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb/).

Top

## How this Information is used

Matchbook will use your Personal Information to:

  1. To process your registration and determine your eligibility for Membership
  2. To conduct appropriate fraud checks
  3. To allow you access and use the Matchbook website
  4. To administer your account
  5. To maintain our own accounts and records
  6. To better understand our Membership profile and tailor our services accordingly
  7. To notify you of additional services that may become available on Matchbook or on websites that we or any of our associated companies might establish
  8. To notify you of promotional events and provide you with promotional materials
  9. To process payments to and from you

If you do not wish to receive future marketing, promotional or sales material from Matchbook, you may contact us to opt-out from this type of communication.

Matchbook may also pass on your Personal Information to trusted third parties in order to assist us with the purposes listed above. Such disclosures to trusted third parties enables us to provide you with the best user experience on our site and shall not be used for the purposes of marketing other goods or services to you. Although we cannot accept responsibility for the actions of third parties, our trusted third parties have strict policies regarding the safeguarding and use of personal information and we have obtained written assurances about their use of your Personal Information.

Matchbook will also retain such information as is necessary to investigate any suspected or actual criminal activity or, in respect of any events listed on Matchbook, any threat, perceived or otherwise, to the integrity of that event and/or breaches of the rules as laid down by the relevant governing body. We reserve the right to pass on any information to any public, regulatory, sporting or other relevant authority as may be required in order to carry out any investigation and prosecution into such matters.

Top

## Security and Encryption

Your Personal Information will be held on secure servers and all transactions are encrypted using secure socket layer (SSL) advanced encryption technology up to 128-bit encryption.

Please note that email communications with Matchbook are NOT encrypted or otherwise secured against outside interference; please use discretion when providing personal details via email. Once we receive your data, it will be held by us on secure servers and we will use all reasonable commercial efforts to ensure it’s security.

Top

## Cookies

### What are cookies?

Cookies are pieces of information in the form of very small text files that a website stores in a user's browser and can retrieve whilst a user is browsing the website in order to identify the user and understand the user's activity. Matchbook uses cookies on our website to improve its performance and your user experience.

### What type of cookies does Matchbook use?

When you use the Matchbook website the following types of cookies can be set on your device:

  1. Session Cookies: these are stored on a user's device and remain there until the termination of the session of a given browser. Stored information is then permanently removed from the device memory. Session Cookies Mechanism does not allow Matchbook to access any personal data or private information from a user's device.
  2. Persistent Cookies: these are stored on a user's device and remain there until deleted. Termination of the session of a given browser does not cause their removal from the user's device. Persistent Cookies Mechanism do allow Matchbook to access personal data or private information from a user's device.

### What does Matchbook use cookies for?

#### Session management

Cookies are used for authenticating a user in the website, securing the user's session in the website and facilitating the correct configuration of the user’s preferred website functions.

Example: Identifying you as being signed in to Matchbook.com and keeping you logged in throughout your visit.

#### Personalisation

These cookies allow the website to remember choices a user makes and provide enhanced experience and more personalised features. They allow the user to personalise the content of the website according to user preferences, recognition of the user's device and its location and displaying the web pages accordingly, remembering user's settings and personalising user's interface.

Example: Remembering your preference for type of odds type, language or currency.

#### Tracking 

Matchbook uses Google Analytics that set their own cookies. These cookies are used to collect statistical information about visitors of the website and the pages they view. These cookies do not collect information that identifies a visitor. All information these cookies collect is aggregated and used anonymously.

**Example:**  Understanding what content is popular to helps us to improve our website.

#### Third party cookies

Some cookies that have been set on our websites are not related to Matchbook.com. When you visit a page with content embedded from, for example, Twitter or YouTube, these service providers may set their own cookies on your web browser. We do not control the use of these cookies and cannot access them, as cookies can only be accessed by the party who originally set them. Please inspect the cookie policy of the third party for further details.

More information about cookies and details of how to manage or disable them can be found on www.aboutcookies.org.

PLEASE NOTE: We strongly recommend that you permit the use of cookies; if you choose to disable cookies by modifying the settings in your browser then you may find that certain sections of the Website do not work as they should, and we do not accept any liability to you for any losses you incur as a result of this.
